jazzcinemas.com 2015-08-24

# JAZZ CINEMAS

## PRIVACY

This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered on the www.jazzcinemas.com website operated by Jazz Cinemas Private Limited. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the Jazz Cinemas site. Usage of the Jazz Cinemas website is conditional upon you agreeing to be bound by this privacy policy.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

#### NATURE OF INFORMATION

Information is gathered for a range of purposes, including the provision of ongoing Customer support and the compiling of Customer databases to enable us to more accurately market our goods and services. The type of information we collect includes such things as contact details, buying habits, opinions, product preferences and transactional details. Jazz Cinemas treats all such information which is collected and identifiable as relating to an individual as Personal Information. It is this information which is described as "Personal Information" for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Personal Information may be collected about Customers via the following means:

  * Competition entry forms
  * Application forms
  * Email
  * Websites (including in some instances cookies)
  * Online transactions
  * Networking functions (e.g.: business cards)
  * Over the phone
  * Credit card details via credit card purchases
  * Information collected from third parties

### CUSTOMER CONSENT

Wherever practical, Jazz Cinemas will obtain the express consent of Customers to the collection of Personal Information. In some situations, Jazz Cinemas will interpret a Customer's actions as indicating that a Customer consents to the collection of Personal Information. This may occur where the Customer has provided Personal Information for a particular purpose and that purpose cannot be achieved without Jazz Cinemas making use of the Customer's Personal Information.

#### WHAT HAPPENS IF PERSONAL INFORMATION IS NOT PROVIDED

Where relevant, Jazz Cinemas will endeavour to make Customers aware that Jazz Cinemas may not be able to provide a proper service to them if Personal Information is not provided upon request.

#### MAINTENANCE AND MANAGEMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

#### WHO MAY VIEW PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * In general, only officers, employees or contractors of Jazz Cinemas may view Personal Information.
  * Jazz Cinemas will only grant access to parties other than Jazz Cinema's officers, employees and contractors to view Personal Information where Jazz Cinemas believes that access is necessary to achieve the purpose for which the Personal Information was collected.

#### JAZZ CINEMAS WILL ONLY DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO PARTIES OTHER THAN JAZZ CINEMAS' OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES AND CONTRACTORS IF:

  * That disclosure is required to give effect to the purposes for which Jazz Cinemas collected the Personal Information.
  * The Customer has consent to that disclosure.
  * Jazz Cinemas believes that the disclosure may lessen a risk of harm to the health or safety of any person.
  * Jazz Cinemas believes an unlawful activity is being undertaken and the Personal Information is disclosed as part of Jazz Cinema's investigation into this activity.
  * Jazz Cinemas is required by law to disclose the Personal Information.
  * The disclosure is required for the enforcement of a criminal law or a law imposing a pecuniary penalty or for the protection of public revenue.

#### UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Jazz Cinemas regularly monitors the quality and accuracy of Personal Information that it maintains and where practical, updates that information on a regular basis. Customers can update their Personal Information at any time by contacting us.

### COMPETITIONS

Personal information gathered during competitions run by Jazz Cinemas will be governed by the principles set out in this Privacy Policy unless an express statement is made in relation to privacy in the conditions of entry for the competition.

### CONTRACTORS

Jazz Cinemas may from time to time employ subcontractors to provide services to it. In these situations, Personal Information may be collected about those subcontractors. This Privacy Policy applies equally to those subcontractors.

### GOOGLE ANALYTICS COOKIES

  * We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics.
  * Our web pages use "cookies" such as but not limited to the Google Analytics or Google advertising cookies to understand and serve you better.
  * A user can set on their browser to notify when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service To opt out of the Google Analytics please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

#### MODIFICATIONS TO THIS DOCUMENT

Jazz Cinemas may modify this Privacy Policy and the way it handles Personal Information at any time in its sole discretion.
